{
    "id": "5627d475934f46e1863c487725e9b86e",
    "title": "Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The injured …………………………. to hospital.",
            "description": "In the simple past, the passive verb form is made with was/were + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "were took",
                "taken",
                "were taken"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The parcel ……………………………. in the morning.",
            "description": "In the simple past, the passive verb form is made with was/were + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "has sent",
                "had sent",
                "was sent"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "All of my friends ………………………………….",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have invited",
                "have been invited",
                "was invited"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The matter ………………………………. by the committee.",
            "description": "In the present continuous, the passive verb form is made with is/am/are + being + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "is being discussed",
                "is discussing",
                "has being discussed"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "English …………………………….. in many parts of the world.",
            "description": "In the simple present, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "spoken",
                "has spoken",
                "is spoken"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Milk …………………………….. by cows and goats.",
            "description": "In the simple present, the passive form is made with is/am/are + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "is given",
                "is being given",
                "has given"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "He ………………………………. by a speeding car.",
            "description": "In the simple past, the passive verb form is made with was/were + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "ran over",
                "was ran over",
                "was run over"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "The hall ………………………………… decorated.",
            "description": "In the present continuous, the passive verb form is made with is/are + being + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "has",
                "is being",
                "had"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "A novel ……………………………….. by him.",
            "description": "In the past continuous, the passive verb form is made with was/were + being + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "was reading",
                "was being read",
                "has read"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The messenger …………………………….",
            "description": "In the simple past, the passive verb form is made with was/were + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "arrested",
                "has arrested",
                "was arrested"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Stray dogs ……………………………. by her.",
            "description": "In the simple present, the passive verb form is made with is/am/are + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "are feeding",
                "are fed",
                "have fed"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The books …………………………………. by me.",
            "description": "In the past perfect, the passive verb form is made with had + been + past participle. ",
            "answers": [
                "had returned",
                "had been returned",
                "were returning"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}